Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place.
That the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary.
Till someone proves it real.
Through it all.
Through all the trouble and times.
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend.
We are, we are on a cruise.
We are?
There's absolutely no way we'll make
it to the Grand Line in this condition.
You're right, we're going to
need a whole lot more meat.
Eating fruit every day is for the birds.
We'll also need some booze.
Shut up, you boneheads!
That's not what I mean.
The Grand Line's a dangerous place.
We'll need more than beer
and meat to survive there.
Not to mention the place is crawling with
pirates who are also in
search of the one piece.
And they all have ships that
are way better than this!
And we don't have a crew.
We don't have a crew, we
don't have any equipment,
or even a real ship for that matter.
There is no way we'll
ever make it like this.
Yep, we'll need a cook, and maybe
a musician to keep us entertained?
A musician?
So stupid?
A little to the south of here is an
island with some settlements on it.
And it looks like we
might be able to get our
ship and some of the
supplies we need there!
Fresh meat at last!
Lots of booze as well
Sound the alarm! They're here!
They're here and they're
gonna kill us all!
Oh no! Pirates! Pirates!
Pirates are attacking! Run!
Everybody run for your
lives! Pirates! Pirates!
Everybody run!
Pirates are coming!
Their bloodlust is unquenchable!
We're doomed.
The pirates are...
Lie!
That hurt!
You little liar!
You're not gonna get away this time!
Wait, wait, wait!
Now run!
Just try and catch me!
Come on, slowpokes!
Ah, man!
Looks like he got away again!
That kid's a Newgate troublemaker.
He'd better hope I
never get a hold of him.
Looks like nobody's getting
a hold of him today.
Ah, yet another job well done.
It is my solemn duty to send the wind of
excitement through this boring old village.
There he is!
Hmm?
Hey, you guys, what's going on?
I bid you, good morning, captain Usopp!
Fear not, your loyal crew, the
Usopp Pirates, have arrived!
Pepper! Carrot!
It's just you two?
Where's Onion?
Have you seen him around today?
Sound the alarm! They're
here! They're here!
They're here and they're
gonna kill us all!
Hey, it's Onion.
I wonder what he's freaking out about?
Pirates!
They're here!
Run for your lives!
Pirates!
We don't stand a chance!
Bloodthirsty murderers!
If Lincoln run, everybody run!
Stop playing!
I'm not playing!
It's for real?
Yes, it's for real!
Pirates are here!
Gotta go!
Time for me to have my snack! You chicken!
Actually, I'm sick! Yeah, I have!
I'll die if I don't eat my snackiosis!
You liar!
You always told us that
you wanted to become
a real pirate someday
and now's our chance!
Yeah, what's with you?
What kind of a pirate is
afraid of other pirates?
If I recall correctly, it
was Buggy the Clown's mark.
Buggy the Clown?
I think I'll just...
But I only saw two tiny boats.
And there were just three people.
It's go time, brave Usa pirates!
We do have a village to protect.
Let's go, men! Move out!
Sir!
Feels good to be on dry land again.
There's a village around
here somewhere, right?
Yeah.
It looks like a small one, though.
Ooh! Ooh!
Then there's meat!
There's meat!
There has to be a place to
eat meat in this village!
Just forget about meat
for a minute, would ya?
Careful.
We're being watched. Huh?
By who? Where are they?
They got meat?
Look out!
That's so cool!
Is this supposed to be
when we're impressed?
I am Usopp, leader of the invincible nation
of pirates who reign over this island.
You stand before a living legend, the
most revered pirate who ever lived.
I am the great Captain Usopp.
Surely you know that plotting an attack
on this island would mean certain death.
My army of 80 million super mean pirate
soldiers would squash you like bugs.
Awesome!
You expect us to believe that?
She knows.
Yep.
Well, now I know.
How can I have been so dumb?
I practically told her I was lying!
I'm such an idiot!
So stupid!
What?
He was lying?
Curse you, you crafty tactician!
80 million may have been an exaggeration,
but I have a great many
men under my control!
My guess is three.
She does know!
Hey, where are you guys going? Come back!
That's pretty cool!
Shut your mouth, or I'll shut it for you!
I'm a proud man, and I won't stand for it!
This is your last warning, or you'll
get to see why they call me...
Proud Usopp, and not pushover Usopp.
Is that clear?
You've already seen for yourself
just how good I am with this thing.
So, you know I can rival
anyone carrying a pistol.
Now that you've drawn your
pistol, are you willing to use it?
Guns aren't for threats,
they're for actions.
Are you willing to risk your life?
Real pirates definitely
have a lot more punch behind
their words because they
can actually back them up.
That's so cool.
I stole that. Huh?
I stole those words from
Red-Haired Shanks, a pirate I know.
What?
You know Red-Haired Shanks?
You really are a real pirate.
Wait, you gotta be lying.
Do you really know him? Yep.
I know your dad, too.
His name's Yasop, right? Huh?
You're right.
My old man's name is Yasop.
But how, uh, how in the
world do you know him?
This is good, huh?
So I met your dad when
I was just a little kid.
Hold on, does my old
man really know Shanks?
Know him.
When I met your dad, he
was part of Shanks' crew,
so they were probably pretty good friends.
I can't believe it!
My old man's sailing the high
seas with famous pirates.
I haven't heard from him in a while,
but I bet he's still with them.
He was a heck of a sharpshooter.
I'd keep him on my crew.
Whoa! Good shot!
Eh, that's nothing.
I could shoot an ant between
the eyes from across town.
You know something, Luffy?
I got a kid named Usopp, and
he's just about your age.
You told me about him
already, a hundred times.
A hundred?
Well, too bad.
I'm telling you again.
It broke my heart to
leave, but I had to go.
You see, Luffy, when the pirate flag
beckons, you must hate its call.
He used to go on and on
and on about his son.
I think I heard enough about
you to make my ears bleed.
And let me tell you,
he was a great pirate.
Yeah, really?
I sure am proud of my old man.
He leapt into a pirate's
life on the endless sea.
And chose a life of real adventure.
Maybe you can help us.
Do you know someone who could
provide us with a decent ship,
or even anyone who knows
how to sail for that matter?
Well, it's a pretty small village.
Sorry, but I just don't think
we'll be able to help you.
What about that huge mansion?
The one on top of that hill over there.
Hey, do you know the Moosop?
With all that money, surely
they can help us get our boat.
You stay away from there!
I just remembered something
that I really gotta do.
Everybody knows me at this place,
so stay and eat as much as you want.
Well, I gotta go!
Why was he in such a
hurry to get out of here?
Are you sure this is
the place they took him?
Yeah, those terrible
pirates dragged him inside,
and now it's up to us to save our captain.
But guys, those are real pirates.
What if they've grilled
and eaten him already?
It's grisly old witch hag to
eat their victims, not pirates!
This is going to be the most brutal
and epic battle of our lives.
We must show no mercy because
they'll never show it to us.
The Usopp pirates have arrived!
Who are these kids?
Captain Usopp is gone. Did they?
Vice up, you filthy pirates!
What have you done with
our beloved captain?
Tell us now!
Yeah, tell us now!
That meat sure was good.
What meat?
These pirates are cannibals!
What have you done, you savages?
If you're looking for your captain...
We ate him.
Ah, careful!
What are you punks looking at me for?
You just had to say
something stupid, didn't you?
You wish to see Usopp.
Don't start this again.
May I see him?
I like talking to him.
No, ma 'am.
That man is without a
doubt a chronic liar.
For someone in your weakened state,
Usopp's outlandish stories
might be too much to handle.
Your late parents instructed me to protect
you to the fullest of my abilities.
It would be against their wishes
for you to see him, Miss Kaya.
Now then, I'll leave
your medicine right here.
Please be sure to take it.
Killjoy.
Killjoy will do.
A name I'll bear if you are kept safe.
Usopp, you came! Of course. How are you?
You seem a little down.
I guess I am.
I'm tired of talking like this.
I'd like to invite you
inside like a proper guest.
But there's just no way
Klahadore would ever allow that.
He's not a bad person,
though. Don't sweat it.
Remember, I'm a brave warrior of the sea
who likes endless oceans and the open sky.
Houses weren't made for rogues like me.
I'd probably just feel cramped in there.
So what adventure are you
going to tell me about today?
Hmm.
Well, let's see.
Oh, I know.
What about the story of me
fighting a giant goldfish
at the South Pole when I
was only five years old?
A goldfish?
A giant goldfish!
What first astounded me was
the immense size of its poop!
It was so big that when I landed on
it, I thought it was solid ground!
It looked like an island!
Wow!
This place is huge!
And if our captain ran off at this hour,
then this is the place he's going to be.
Oh, what in the world
does Usopp come here for?
He comes to lie. To lie? That's terrible.
He's not a bad guy.
He's great, isn't he?
Yeah, he's awesome.
How is a liar awesome?
Well, Kaya,
the girl who lives there has been
in a terrible depression that's kept
her weak and in bed since her
parents got sick and died a year ago.
She's very rich, but all that money
couldn't help her recover from her sadness.
So our captain tells us special made-up
stories to make her laugh and cheer her up.
Captain Isop is the best at telling lies.
Wow, that really is pretty nice of him.
Yeah!
The best thing about him
is his mischievous side.
He's always up to something.
I like him because he's
not afraid to be silly.
And I like the captain's crazy lies.
So when he tells her those
stories, he makes her feel better?
Yep, lots better. Great!
I think we should ask
her for a ship after all!
Getting in is impossible.
Those guards at the gate
don't let anyone through.
Oh, where's Luffy?
I'll go ask her!
No, you're not gonna...
No!
Pardon the intrusion!
No, no, no, no, no!
So after that terrifying and
traumatic little incident,
we escaped into the sky riding
on a giant slingshot ball!
What's that?
Yahoo!
That worked well.
My goodness, are you okay?
Ah, don't mind them, Kaya.
This happens to me all the time.
That's just the price of
being a famous adventurer.
They're just new recruits who heard about
me and came to join the Usopp Pirates.
Nope, not me.
I came here to see you.
I wanted to ask you a favor.
A favor from me? Uh-huh.
I was wondering if there was any
way you could help us get a boat.
You there.
What do you think you're doing?
Klahadore.
Get out.
I'll have you know that this
is criminal trespassing.
These people are...
Not now, Kaya.
You can tell me all about this
riffraff after they've left.
Now get out, all of you.
Leave now, unless you have
some business with me.
All right.
Do you think you could help us get a ship?
Certainly not.
Usopp! Oh, crap!
You have quite the reputation.
You are very well known in the village.
Quite impressive for
someone as young as you!
Usually people who admire
me so much call me Captain.
So it's Captain Usopp to you.
Your father also had something
of a reputation. What?
You'll never be anything more
than the son of a filthy pirate.
Who knows what sort of
trouble you're up to now?
All I ask is that you and your kind
leave this respectable young lady alone.
A filthy pirate?
You and she are from completely
different worlds, and you know it.
Is it money you're after?
How much do you want?
Cease this at once, Klahadore!
Apologize to him!
Hey, calm down, Kaya.
I don't believe there is any reason to
apologize to this savage young man, my lady.
My goal isn't to slander.
I am merely stating the truth.
I sympathize with your situation.
You must hate your
great idiot of a father?
For abandoning his family and his village.
because of his mindless lust for treasure.
Clador, stop!
Don't you dare insult
my father ever again!
Usopp?
Why have you gotten so worked up, Usopp?
It's times like these when you
should do what you do best and lie.
Tell me about how your father
is really a traveling salesman,
or about how you aren't
really related by blood.
Captain!
Case in point.
He resorts to violence.
I guess the apple never falls
far from the tree, does it?
Shut up!
My father listened to his heart and
chose a life of risk and adventure.
I am proud to say that my old man
is a brave warrior of the sea.
You're right, I have been known
to exaggerate from time to time,
but I will never lie
about who my father is.
I refuse to be ashamed of my heritage.
I am the son of a pirate.
Captain.
Pirates are brave warriors
of the sea, are they?
That's quite a twisted
way of putting things.
You don't seem to understand that you
are living proof of his savage blood.
You run around spouting lies and use
violence when you don't get your way.
To top it off, you cozy up to the lady
of the house to steal her fortune.
You're wrong! I only...
Your father is a filthy, Newgate pirate!
Treachery is in your blood!
Of course you would have
such an evil scheme!
You won't let up, will you?
Stop it, Usopp, please!
No more violets!
I can't take it!
Lahador isn't a bad person.
He's just trying to do what he thinks is
best for me, and sometimes he goes too far.
Leave this place.
You are never to come here again!
Yeah, I get it.
You don't have to tell me twice, buddy.
This is the last you'll ever see of me.
Usopp.
Hey, you butler jerk!
Our captain's not that kind of guy!
Shut up, you don't have
a bone to pick with him.
You're a bunch of dope!
Pull me down! Pull me down!
I'm gonna kick his ass!
You will all leave immediately!
Your meal is ready now, Miss Kaya.
Thank you.
I don't want it.
The cook would be most
upset to hear you say that.
He works his hardest day and night to come
up with delicious meals
that suit your needs.
Why were you so cruel to him?
I know I was wrong to talk
to Usopp without telling you.
I will admit that much, and I'm very
sorry for not being honest with you.
But this situation did not
warrant that harsh treatment.
May I sit down?
Go ahead.
It has been quite some time since
I first arrived at this house.
Soon it will be three years that I have
been in the service of your family.
I will never forget what happened when
I showed up at your father's door.
My former employers were
brutal, pitiless men.
I had been kicked off the ship I worked
on for some small blunder I had made,
and with no work or money, I was on
the verge of dying like a beggar.
As far as I know, I would have
died without your father's help.
I owe my life to your parents.
And now that they're gone,
I owe my life to you.
I know that it isn't my place to
interfere with your friendships.
I wouldn't have taken such a bold step
unless I thought it absolutely necessary.
It's just that Usopp isn't exactly
known for his upstanding character.
You see,
if anything were to happen to you it
would be my fault for not seeing to
your safety and I would never be able
to ask forgiveness from your parents.
Did you think ill of me for my
childish behavior earlier today?
No, of course I don't.
I'm thankful to have you
around too, Klahadore.
But I stand by my opinion.
Usopp is one of the nicest people I know.
We'll see about that.
Until then, he is still not welcome here.
Clawhead door!
You blockhead!
Blockhead will do just fine.
Where'd Luffy go?
Who knows?
He probably ran after that captain.
I bet he's at his secret spot.
Yeah, over by the shore.
He always goes there when he's
going to think something over.
Luffy can take care of himself,
but where's your other friend?
Oh, yeah, Onion.
Come to think of it, he just
up and disappears a lot.
Yeah, and then he shows up out
of nowhere, all freaked out.
Terrible news, guys!
You see?
Listen to me!
Some nut job is on his way here
and he only walks backwards!
You liar!
It's the truth!
There he is! Hmm?
Now which one of you people
has the nerve to call me weird?
I'm just a normal guy.
That's so.
You look insane. Don't be silly.
I'm just an ordinary
run-of-the-mill hypnotist.
A hypnotist? Really? Awesome!
Show us something!
Yeah, do something!
What?
You fools!
What makes you think that I
would want to reveal my masterful
hypnosis techniques to a
bunch of roadside strangers?
Okay, you convinced me.
Now watch the ring closely.
What a ham.
So, by the count of Django,
you'll be in a deep sleep.
All right, are you ready?
One, two, Django!
Who is this freaky weirdo?
Hi!
What are you doing here?
I came here to be alone, but
I guess that's not happening.
Did you follow me?
What do you want?
Oh, you know, nothing.
Ouch.
I can't believe that butler.
Insulting my old man like that.
Yeah, I hate that guy too.
No matter what anyone says,
Yasop was a great pirate.
Yeah, really.
I've always looked up to my old man for
living every day with his life on the line,
out in the open ocean.
He made a brave choice,
and I admire him for that.
And then that stupid, snotty
butler stomped all over my pride.
He's gonna pay for this. Hey, wait.
Do you know if you're ever
gonna see that girl again?
I don't know.
I'll consider it if that butler
apologizes to me for the things he said.
That butler right there?
Yeah, that's the one. If he...
What in the world is he doing down here?
That's a big idea.
Hey, Jango, I specifically ordered
you to keep yourself inconspicuous.
That doesn't mean sleeping in the road.
Relax, man.
I've perfected the
skills of the chameleon.
I blend in.
There's someone else with
him, and man, is he weird.
I've never seen him before.
Who is he?
So, have all the necessary
preparations been made?
But of course.
We can start any time!
On the rich girl murder plan?
Murder?
searching for a great treasure.
I had a map in my mind
that I knew would lead me.
I had to find
my way to that place before
someone could beat me.
The promised land was in my
grasp And I wouldn't let go.
My only dream.
I won't stop chasing
it until it comes true.
But if the world ever changes!
I call out your name.
We return to the time.
When everything's the same.
As long as I'm with you.
My memories won't fade.
Waiting for that one true dream?